http://www.guixt.com/company/privacy

Your SAP ERP
Get what you want. Choose your SAP ERP.
Doc. - Offline for Scanguns
Doc. - Liquid UI WebScript (WS)
Material Management Console
SDK (Server and Designer)
Docs - Liquid UI
WebScript (WS)
Doc. - Liquid UI
WebScript (WS)
Console
SDK (Server and Designer)
Privacy Policy, effective as of January 22, 2018
This Privacy Policy covers use and disclosure of information that we collect through our website, www.guixt.com/www.liquid-ui.com, related applications, our services and programs offered by Synactive. The use of information obtained through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the customer has engaged Synactive, Inc.
User Data
Synactive respects the privacy of our account users, website visitors, customers and the privacy of their data. All user data contained within the email, applications, attached logs, forms, webinars, surveys and documents you may use or compose with the Synactive(/Liquid UI/GuiXT) Service are governed by the Synactive Terms of Use, Synactive Terms of Service, Synactive Service Agreement, and Synactive End User Agreement. We will not utilize, sell, or rent your data uploaded into our system.
You may choose to stop receiving our email updates by following the unsubscribe instructions included in the email or you can contact us at rfi@guixt.com.
Data Collection
We collect the e-mail addresses and certain personal information of those who communicate with us via e-mail or register with us to provide requested service. We also collect certain information regarding which pages users access or visit, and information volunteered by the users (such as any surveys Synactive might conduct and/or website registrations). When you request a Free Trial for the Synative Software, we ask for the following information: your name, telephone number, valid email address and more through which we may contact you. We receive the following information, including but not limited to, your name, telephone number, valid email address, either through in-app forms, or our internal servers ios.guixt.com and ps.liquid-ui.com, to enhance your experience with Liquid UI.
We may receive information about you from external sources, including third parties from whom we have purchased data or openly available databases, and merge this information with data we already have about you. This helps us to enhance and analyze our records, identify new clients, and provide services and products that may be of interest to you.
Synactive may also collect and analyze certain information regarding the use of the Synactive website and services available therein from visitors and users. Information collected may include but is not limited to website traffic, visits frequency, type of browser, operating system, etc.
Use of Information
We may use your personal information to provide the requested services, including services that display personalized emails, documents, and forms. Also, we may use personal information for analysis and research to operate and improve the Synactive website, product, and service.
We do not share/sold collected information to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide services or products you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We may be required to disclose information to law enforcement or in response to a court order or other government requirement.
We may also disclose information which in our judgment is necessary to avoid liability or injury to our company or our customers.
To investigate potential violations of the Synactive Terms of Use, Synactive Terms of Service, Synactive Service Agreement, and Synactive End User Agreement.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Synactive and our analytics provider use cookies to help us monitor the use of our website so that we can better understand what information is most valuable to our users. We use technologies such as cookies, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, to track users’ activities around the website/application, and to gather demographic information about our user. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.
Analytics/ Log Files
As is true of most websites and applications, we gather certain information which includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.
We use this information, which does not identify individuals, to analyze trends, to administer the website, to track users’ activities around the website and to gather demographic information about our users.
We do link some of this automatically-collected data to identifiable information. This allows us to deliver a better user experience by reducing data entries that need to be entered when filling out forms, downloading gated content, completing surveys, etc.
Testimonials
With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at rfi@guixt.com.
Information Related to Data Collected for through the Synactive Platform
Synactive, Inc. collects information under the direction of its customers and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes.
Security
Synactive has implemented processes intended to protect user information and maintain the security of data. Each account holder is assigned a unique username and password, which is required to access their account. It is each user’s responsibility to protect the security of his or her login information. We keep personal information concerning you on a secure server. It is protected by a firewall and other electronic security from unauthorized access through the Internet or our network. It is also physically secured against intruders. Our staff is provided access on a "need to know" basis only. These policies may not apply to information that is transferred offline, such as information we obtain from the Alliance Partner application. If you have any questions about security on our website and related applications, you can contact us at rfi@guixt.com.
Cancellation or Termination of the Account
If your account is terminated for any reason, please contact us at rfi@guixt.com with any requests to access your data. Please be aware that Synactive may for a time retain residual information in our backup of our data stores and databases. We will respond to your request to access within 30 business days.
Compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act
As a business service, Synactive does not target its offerings toward and does not knowingly collect any personal information from users under 13 years of age.
Other Sites and Business Partners
We provide links that take you to other websites. We encourage you to review the privacy and other policies at third party sites you visit since those websites are not bound to follow our policies.
Changes to this Policy
Synactive may in the future alter or add to this Privacy Policy, especially as we add new products and services. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically check this part of our website for changes.
Questions
Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to rfi@guixt.com or by postal mail at:
Synactive, Inc
1065 E. Hillsdale Blvd., Suite 225
Foster City, CA 94404
Copyright © 1998-2020 Synactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
| Site Map
